너희들 내일 저녁에 뭐해?
Hey, you guys?
What are you doing tomorrow night?
어디보자
내 스케줄은..
Oh, well, let me see.
I believe I'm..
TV보다가 잠드는 거야
Yes, falling asleep in front of the TV.
매니저가 괜찮은 연극표
여섯장을 구해줬거든
Well, my agent hooked me up
with six tickets to a great play.
나 연극 보면서도 잘수 있어
I could fall asleep at a play.
- 무슨 연극인데?
- 여자 1인극인데
- What is it?
- It's a one-woman play called:
왜 날 싫어해?: 한 성난
여자의 인생기야
Why Don't You Like Me?
A Bitter Woman's Journey Through Life.
- 재미있겠다!
- 그래
- That sounds interesting.
- That does sound interesting.
두시간 동안 여자의 푸념을
듣고 있어야 하다니 보나마나..
To listen to a woman complain for
two hours. I don't think it gets bet..
맞아! 우리 여자들 운전도 하고
투표도 하고, 일도 할수 있어!
I know! I know. We can drive.
We can vote. We can work.
그런데 뭘 더 바라는 거야?
What more do these broads want?
다들 좋은 시간이 될거야
내가 약속할게
Well, you guys will have a great time.
I promise.
뭐야? 넌 안가?
What? How come you don't have to go?
가고 싶은데
I wish I could, but I found out..
다음날 아침 일찍
촬영이 있어서 난 안되겠어
that I have to be at work really early
the next day, so I can't go.
남은 표는 너희들이
아무나 초대해
But take the extra ticket
and invite whoever you want.
어디보자
내가 싫어하는 사람이 누구더라?
Let's see. Who do I hate?
오, 미안해
Oh, sorry.
미안
- Oops, sorry.
- Okay.
자, 이러면 됐지?
- Okay. Up we go.
그래!
- Oh, gosh, okay!
- All right.
물어볼게 있어
Can I ask you a question?
친구끼리 큰 의미 두지 않고
Do you think it's possible
for two friends to fool around..
부비적 거리는게 가능할까?
and not have it be a big deal?
아니, 그건 말도 안되지
그런데 왜?
No, I don't think that ever works. Why?
- 그냥
- 잠깐, 레이첼?
- No reason.
- No, no. Rachel?
- 누구랑 그러고 싶은데?
- 그런거 아냐!
- Who do you want to fool around with?
- Nobody! Forget it.
조이?
Joey?
어쩌면
Maybe.
- 절대 안돼!
- 왜?
- You can't.
- Why?
그야..!
Because!
방금 네가 한말
하나도 못 알아듣겠어
Okay, seriously, did not understand
a word you just said.
- 밖으로 나와
- 알았어
- In the hall.
- Okay.
- 조이랑 그러고 싶어?
- 그래
- You wanna fool around with Joey?
- Yeah.
지난번 조이 꿈꾼 뒤로
머리에서 떠나지가 않아
Ever since I had that dream about him,
I can't get it out of my head.
뭐 어때? 다른 사람들도
다들 그러는데
I mean, what's the big deal?
People do it all the time.
누가?
누가 친구사이에 그러는데?
Who do you know that are friends
that just fool around?
좋아, 우선 생각나는 사람이..
돈과 재닛
Okay. Off the top of my head..
Don and Janet.
- 그게 누군데?
- 회사 사람들이야
- Who are they?
- I know them from work.
- 둘다?
- 아니, 한사람만
- Both of them?
- No, just one of them.
어느쪽?
Which one?
몰라
내가 방금 누구라고 했니?
I don't know.
What were the names I just said?
안돼, 레이첼
대책없이 복잡해 질거야
No, Rachel, things could get
incredibly complicated.
알았어! 네말이 맞아
조이랑 아무짓 안할게, 난 다만..
All right. You're right. I won't do anything
with Joey. I just thought it..
타라곤 두컵에 베이킹 소다 1파운드
붉은 양파 한개라고?
Okay, so that's two cups of tarragon,
one pound of baking soda and a red onion?
대체 뭘 만들건데?
What the hell are you cooking?
프렌즈 시즌 9
'비밀파티!'
오늘 내가 무슨일
해야하는지 알면 기절할거다
You guys won't believe
what I have to do for work today.
공룡에 대해 떠드는 직업을
선택한건 너 자신이야!
Yes, but, Ross, you chose a career
of talking about dinosaurs.
우리과에 교수 두명이
새로 오거든
There are these two professors
who are joining my department..
여기서 만나서
캠퍼스 안내해 줘야해
and I have to meet them here
and show them around campus.
그게 뭐가 힘들어?
What's so bad about that?
팔꿈치에 가죽 댄 재킷을 입은
I just know they'll be
a couple of old windbags..
고리타분한 노인네들 일거야
wearing tweed jackets
with suede elbow patches.
오빠?
Ross?
왜? 이건 가죽 아냐
What? These aren't suede.
실례합니다
사람을 찾고 있는데요
Excuse me. I'm looking for someone.
혹시 로스 겔러라는분
알아요?
You don't, by any chance,
know a Ross Geller?
아뇨
No.
안녕하세요?
제가 로스 겔러입니다
Hi. Hi, I'm Ross Geller.
윌러 교수예요
Oh, hi. I'm Professor Wheeler.
오! 정말 다행이네요!
Oh, that's.. That's..
That's nice.
반가워요
It's good to meet you.
캠퍼스 안내를 맡아주셔서
정말 고마워요
Thank you so much for taking the time
to show me around.
뭘요
No, it's no big deal.
이 약속 아니었으면
운동이나 하고 있었을 거예요
If I weren't doing this, I'd just,
you know, be at the gym working out.
우리한테 소개시켜줄까?
Is he gonna introduce us?
지금 로스눈엔 우리가
안들어 올걸?
I think we're just blurry shapes
to him now.
지리적 고립과 빠른 돌연변이
By the way,
I really enjoyed your paper..
발생에 대한 논문 흥미로웠어요
on the connection between geographic
isolation and rapid mutagenesis.
오! 하룻밤만에 쓴걸요
I wrote that in one night.
두사람 한달안에
결혼하는데 20달러 건다
Twenty bucks says they're married
within the month.
그럼 이만 갈까요?
Well, we should probably get going.
봐야할 곳이 많거든요
You know, we've got a lot
of ground to cover.
다른 교수님도
오시기로 돼있잖아요?
Isn't another professor
supposed to come with us?
금시초문인데요?
I don't think so.
맞아요, 코넬대학에서 오신
스파포드 교수님이요
I'm pretty sure.
A Professor Spafford from Cornell?
그럼 늦으시나 보네요
Well, he's obviously late,
and the rule in my class is:
지각할거면 아예 들어오지
말라는게 제 강의 규칙이죠
If you can't come on time,
then don't come at all.
많은 학생들이 그 규칙을
잘 따르고 있어요
An option that many of my students use.
- 가실까요?
- 기다리지 않아도 될까요?
- Shall we?
- We shouldn't wait for him?
다 큰 어른인걸요
잘 찾아 올겁니다
You know what, he's a big boy.
I'm sure he'll find us, okay?
- 겔러 교수?
- 빌어먹을!
- Professor Geller?
- Oh, damn it!
조이, 잔 로저스예요
오늘 저녁 파티 기대 되요
Hi, Joey, it's Jan Rogers.
Can 't wait for your party tonight.
자기 집 주소를 잊어버렸어요
전화좀 줘요, 안녕
Listen, I forgot your address.
Can you give me a call? Thanks. Bye.
무슨일 있어?
What's happening?
그래, 오늘 저녁 연극에
네가 못온다니 유감이야
It's a real shame you can't make it
to that one-woman show tonight.
내일 일찍 일어나야 하거든
I'd love to, but I gotta get up
so early the next day.
- 알다시피 나한텐 일이 우선이야
- 그래, 알지
- You know me, work comes first.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
조이, 잔 로저스예요
오늘 저녁 파티 기대되네요
Hi, Joey, it's Jan Rogers.
Can 't wait for your party tonight.
멍청한 잔 로저스!
Stupid Jan Rogers!
오늘 네가 파티 열어?
You are having a party tonight?
- 아냐
- 조이!
- No.
- Joey!
맞아
Yeah.
그게 말야.. 우리 인생의 나날들 팀을
위해 여는 파티야
I'm kind of having a thing
for the Days of Our Lives people.
그런데 우리한테 말을 안해?
And you weren't gonna tell us?
우리한테 들키지 않고
넘어갈수 있다고 생각했어?
How did you think you were
gonna get away with that?
매년 그래왔는걸
I do it every year.
매년 파티를 했다구?
You do that every year?!
그말을 내가 왜 했지?!
I didn't have to tell you that!
난 잔 로저스보다
더 멍청해!
God, I'm stupider than Jan Rogers!
그래서 연극표 줬구나!
우리 따돌리려구!
That's why you got us tickets
to that play, to get rid of us!
맞아
Yeah.
작년에 우리를 중세식 식당에
보낸것도 파티 때문이었고?!
Last year is that why you sent us
to that Medieval Times restaurant?
맞아
Yeah.
재작년에 단추공장 야간관람
시켜준것도 그 때문이었고?
And the year before that, you set up that
nighttime tour of that button factory?
그게 먹혀들 줄은
정말 몰랐어
I can't believe you guys went
for that one.
네 파티에 왜 우릴
초대하지 않는거야?
Why wouldn't you invite us
to your parties?
넌 괜찮지만 다른 애들은
배우들 앞에서 바보같이 굴잖아!
You're fine, okay? But everyone else acts
like an idiot around famous people.
그럼 나만 초대해
Well, then, so just invite me.
좋아, 솔직히 말하지!
네가 제일 심해!
Please, I was trying to be nice.
You're the worst one.
그러지 말고 나 초대해줘!
주책 안부린다고 약속할게
Joey, come on! Please, please?
Let me come. I will behave. I promise.
- 정말이야, 제발 제발 제발!
- 알았어, 그럼 와
- I will behave. Please, please, please.
- Okay, fine. You can come.
다른 애들한테는 비밀이다
옥상에서 8시에 시작해
But don't tell anybody else.
It's up on the roof at 8.
옥상파티?
A soap-opera roof party?!
내가 스타들의 옥상파티에 초대되다니!
이럴수가! 믿어지지가 않아!
I'm going to a soap-opera roof party!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
정말 엄청난 일이구나!
And it's out of my system.
그리고 아내와 유람선을 타고
갈라파고스에 갔습니다
And then my wife and I went
on a cruise to the Galapagos.
해산물 뷔페가 있었는데
기가 막히더군요
There was a seafood buffet
you wouldn't believe.
대합, 홍합, 굴
There were clams and mussels
and oysters..
금게
and cracked crab..
눈게
and snow crab..
왕게가 있었어요
and king crab.
내가 갑각류에 알레르기가
있는게 안타까웠습니다
It's a pity I'm allergic to shellfish.
학부는 어디서 공부했어요?
So where did you get
your undergraduate degree?
난 갑각류에만
알레르기가 있는게 아닙니다
- And that's not all I'm allergic to.
- Oh, it's not over.
아직 안끝나셨군요
땅콩, 캐슈넛, 아몬드
I'm also allergic to peanuts
and cashews..
개암열매에도 알레르기가 있죠
and almonds and filberts..
결국 넛트류 전부로군요?
So basically all nuts!
흥미롭게도 그렇지가 않습니다
Interestingly, no.
"흥미롭다"는 단어를
아무데나 붙이시네요
You're kind of playing it fast and loose
with the word "interesting."
화장실에 다녀와야겠소
If you'll excuse me,
I'm going to use the restroom.
제가 돌아오면
When I come back,
remind me to tell you..
어떤 종류의 동물털에
알레르기가 있는지 얘기해 드리죠
about the different types
of animal dander I'm allergic to.
오, 이건 악몽이에요!
Oh, my God!
난 삶의 의욕을 잃었어요
I've lost the will to live.
- 우리 저분 따돌려요
- 네?
- Let's ditch him.
- What?
화장실 간 사이에 튀자구요
제발 부탁이에요
While he's still in the bathroom.
I am begging you.
알았어요
그런데 물어볼게 있습니다
Okay. Okay, fine,
but I just have one question for you.
우리 나갈때 어떻게 가죠?
걸어서? 뛰어서?
When we exit, should we walk or run..
성큼성큼? 어슬렁?
or prance or stroll..?
그만! 저분 말은 느려도 볼일은
빨리 볼지 몰라요! 어서 나가요!
Stop it! Stop it! He talks slow,
but he might pee fast. Okay, let's move!
- 하루를 망칠 뻔했는데 다행이에요
- 네, 맞아요
- We actually managed to salvage the day.
- Yeah, we did.
저랑 시간을
보내주셔서 고마워요
Thanks for spending
so much time with me.
화요일에 강의가 없어서
다행이었어요
I'm so lucky it worked out
you don't have class on Tuesday.
그래요
Right.
안녕, 이쪽은 찰리야
Oh, hey, you guys, this is Charlie.
찰리, 이쪽은 피비와
내 동생 모니카예요
Charlie, this is Phoebe
and my sister, Monica.
- 안녕하세요?
- 우리과에 새로 오셨어
- Hi.
- Charlie will be joining my department.
댁도 고생물학자예요?
- You're a paleontologist too?
- Yeah.
절단된 절지동물의
Oh, okay. Now, what do you think..
종의 다양화에 관한 레냐드의
새 이론 어떻게 생각해요?
of Renyard's new theory of species
variegation in segmented arthropods?
좀 억지스럽긴 하지만
흥미로운 개념이에요
Well, I think he's a little out there,
but he does have some interesting ideas.
미안해요
전화좀 받을게요
Oh, I'm sorry. I have to take this.
Excuse me.
종의 다양화에 관한
레냐드의 새 이론?
Renyard's theory of species variegation?
네가 보던 서류에서 보고
너 놀라게 해주려고 외웠어
I saw the article on your coffee table.
I memorized the title to freak you out.
두사람 재미있었어?
So did you two have fun?
말도마! 끝내줘!
Oh, my God. She's great.
우린 공통점도 많고 잘 통해
유머도 있고
We have so much in common,
and she's just cool, you know? And funny.
모를까봐 얘기해주는 건데
미모도 예술이야!
And I don't know if you've noticed,
but she's a hottie!
안녕?
Hi!
안녕
나 몸이 별로 안좋아
Hi, you guys. Listen, you know what,
I'm not feeling really well..
오늘 연극 못보러 가겠어
and I don't think I'm gonna get
to go to the play.
정말? 어디가 아픈데?
Really? What's wrong?
몰라
좀 심각한것 같아
I don't know.
I think it's kind of serious.
아침에 TV보니까
You know, I was watching this thing
on TV this morning..
뉴캐슬병에 대해 나오더라
나 그병 걸린것 같아
about Newcastle disease,
and I think I might have it.
뉴캐슬병은 분비물을 매개로
Newcastle disease is
a secretion-borne virus..
닭과 조류들만 걸리는 병이에요
that only affects chickens
and other poultry.
이사람 누구야?
Okay, who's this?
레이첼, 이쪽은 찰리 윌러
내 동료 교수야
I'm sorry. Rachel, this is Charlie Wheeler.
She's a colleague.
안녕하세요?
악수하고 싶지만
Hi. Well, I would shake your hand..
내 닭병 옮길까봐 못하겠네요
but I'm sure you don't want
to get my chicken disease.
- 레이첼, 나좀 보자
- 그래
- Rachel, can I see you for a second?
- Sure.
너 꾀병이지?
You're not sick.
뭐? 아냐!
What? Yes, I am!
그럼 왜 이렇게 차려입었어?
Okay, then why are you all dressed up?
아프니까 기분전환이라도
해보려고 입은거야!
When you're sick, you do whatever
you can to make yourself feel better.
집에 남아서 조이
꼬시려는 거지?
You just want to stay home
so you can make a move on Joey.
아냐! 지난번에 네말 듣고
포기했어, 그런거 아냐!
No, I heard you before.
That is so not what this is.
그럼 대체 뭐야?
Okay, then what is this?
좋아
Okay.
조이가 옥상에서 동료 배우들
불러서 비밀파티를 연대
Joey is having a secret
Days of Our Lives party up on the roof.
그 연극표는 너희들
따돌리려고 준거야
And he sent you guys to the play
to get rid of you.
뭐?!
What?!
왜? 무슨 일인데?
What? What's going on?
조이가 옥상에서 동료배우들과
비밀파티를 연대!
Joey is having a secret
Days of Our Lives party up on the roof!
조이는 너희한테 비밀로 하라고
했지만 난 말해주려고 온거야
He didn't want you to know about it,
but I came over here to tell you.
- 아프단 말하려고 온것 아니었어요?
- 교수예요? 탐정이에요?
- You came to say you were sick.
- All right, professor or detective?
조이가 파티를 열면서
우릴 초대하지 않았다구?
Wait, Joey's having a party,
and he wasn't gonna invite us?
그것도 매년 해왔대! 우리한테
연극보라고 한것도 파티 때문이었고
He does it every year.
That's why he's sending you to the play.
중세식 식당과 단추공장도
다 파티 때문이었어!
That's why he sent us to that medieval
restaurant and to that button factory.
그 끔찍한 박물관 관람 말이야?
And that horrible museum tour?
그거 내가 계획 짠거야
No, I arranged that.
난 그만 자야겠다
잘 놀다와
Hey, you guys, I'm turning in.
Have fun.
네 파티 얘기 다 들었어!
We know about your party, Joey.
- 무슨 파티?
- 다 끝났으니까 그 가운 벗어!
- What party?
- The game's over. Take off your robe.
알았어
Okay, I mean..
- 안돼! 그만!
- 빨리 입어! 어서!
Close it up! Close it up!
만나서 반가워요
Nice to meet you.
어서 와요! 잘 왔어요!
Hey, you made it! All right!
와줘서 고마워
Glad you could make it.
Thanks for coming.
- 맙소사! 카일 라우더잖아?!
- 안녕?
- Oh, my God. Kyle Lowder!
- Hi.
사랑해요!
I love you!
이래서 초대 안했던거야!
제발 진정해!
Hey. That's why I didn't invite you.
You have to calm down, all right?
가서 뭐라도 좀 마셔라
Just go get yourself a drink
or something.
네가 원하는게 그거야?
내가 자제력 잃는거?
Oh, yeah, that's what you want.
My inhibitions lowered.
스타들한테 둘러 쌓여 있다는게
믿어지지가 않아!
Oh, my God, can you believe
we're surrounded by all this?
내 자신이 통제가 안돼!
I can barely control myself.
모니카, 유부녀라는 사실 잊지마
Monica, you might want to remember
that you're married.
그런데 챈들러는 어디 있어?
Where is Chandler anyway?
어머! 챈들러!
Oh, my God! Chandler!
다들 어떻게 된거야?
Where the hell is everybody?
왜 날 싫어하지?
Why Don't You Like Me?
제 1장: 나의 초경
Chapter 1: My First Period.
조이가 사인은 안된다고 했어!
Hey, Joey said no autographs.
하지만 이왕 해주는 거면
나도 해주세요
But if she's getting one,
I want one too!
"행운"어쩌구 하는거 말고
"모니카에게 사랑을"이라고 써줘요
"To Monica." And none of this
"best wishes" crap. I want "love."
모니카? 매튜는 나한테
전화번호를 준거야
Okay, actually, Mon, Matthew was
giving me his phone number.
어머!
이 파티에 올줄 알았다면
Oh, man! If I had known
I was coming to this party..
결혼 안했을 텐데!
I never would've gotten married!
- 반가웠어요, 레이첼
- 반가워요
- It was nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- 전화해요
- 꼭 할게요!
- Call me.
- We will!
남자들한테 인기 좋구나?
조이에 대한건 다 잊었나봐
Look at you with all the guys!
I guess you've forgotten all about Joey.
그래, 조이에 대해선
다 잊은것 같아
Yeah, well, I guess I have forgotten
about Joey.
그리고 넌 챈들러에 대해
완전히 잊었고 말야
And clearly, you've forgotten
about Chandler.
챈들러는 내 운명인걸
Please. Chandler's the love of my life.
와, 가죽바지, 죽이는데?!
Oh, leather pants! Have mercy!
이런 파티에
자주 참석하나요?
So do you get to go
to things like this often?
물론이죠
여긴 뉴욕이잖아요
Come on, this is New York.
유명한 드라마 스타들과
이런 옥상파티도 하고
I mean, one night you're at a rooftop
party filled with soap stars..
또 다음 밤에는..
and the next night, you're..
사실은, 저도 이런 파티는
생전 처음이에요
Who am I kidding, this is so cool.
보스턴 떠나기가
쉽지 않았겠어요
So it's probably gonna be hard
for you to leave Boston, huh?
실은 떠나서 기뻐요
애인과 헤어졌거든요
Actually, I'm kind of happy to be leaving.
I just broke up with someone.
저런, 유감이네요
Oh, so sad.
그래도 하버드를 떠나는건
쉽지 않았을 거예요
Still, it can't be easy
for you to leave Harvard.
알버트 윈터마이어 같은 노벨상
수상자와 함께 있었잖아요
Especially after working with a Nobel
Prize winner like Albert Wintermeyer.
헤어진 남자친구가
바로 알비예요
Actually, Albie is the guy
I broke up with.
- 알버트 윈터마이어와 사귀었다구요?
- 네
- You dated Albert Wintermeyer?
- Yeah.
그분을 '알비'라고 불러요?
And you called him "Albie"?
마치 알버트 아인슈타인을..
I mean, that's like calling
Albert Einstein..
'알비'라고 부르는것 같군요
Albie.
네, 아주 똑똑한 남자죠
Yeah, well, he is a brilliant man.
방사성 탄소연대 측정법의
You think?
I mean, you dated the guy..
정확성을 개선한 분이에요!
who improved the accuracy
of radiocarbon dating by a factor of 10!
네, 남자가 똑똑하기만 해서
다 용서되는건 아니죠
Yes, and while that is everything
one looks for in a boyfriend..
그사람도 복잡한게 많아요
he had a lot of issues.
어떤거요?
Oh, like what?
캐물어서 미안해요
평범한 사람들이
I'm sorry. I don't mean to pry.
It's just that this must be..
할리우드 뒷얘기 듣는것과
마찬가지라서요
what regular people experience
when they watch Access Hollywood.
뒷얘기 하나 해줄까요?
Okay, you want the dirt?
그는 굉장히
불안정한 사람이에요
Albie was seriously insecure.
내가 전에 만났던 남자에 대해
얼마나 불안해했다고요
He was really intimidated by the guy
I dated before him.
노벨상 수상자를 불안하게
한 사람은 대체 누구죠?
Who's intimidating to a guy
who won the Nobel Prize?
노벨상 두번 탄 사람이요
A guy who won two.
두번?
Two? What..?
설마 벤자민 호바트랑
사귀었다는건 아니겠죠?
Don't tell me you dated
Benjamin Hobart?
맞아요, 3년 사귀었어요
Yeah, for three years.
맙소사!
Oh, my God.
노벨상 안받은 사람과는
사귀어 본적 없어요?
Have you ever been in a relationship with
someone who hasn't won the Nobel Prize?
없어요
No.
아, 첫번째 남자친구
빌리가 있군요
But there was
my first boyfriend, Billy.
노벨상 수상자가 아닌가보죠?
Oh, yeah? No Nobel Prizes for him?
아녜요, "맥아더 천재 장학금"만
받았을 뿐이에요
No, but he did just win
the MacArthur "genius grant."
오, 비교가 안되네요!
What a loser.
포도주 더 마실래요?
Some more wine?
로스, 찰리하고는 잘돼가?
Hey, Ross. How's it going with Charlie?
그럼, 이거 마시고 나서
Oh, great. After I finish my wine..
내 평범한 뇌를 쏴버릴 거야!
I'm gonna blow
my average-sized brains out.
무슨 일이야?
What's the matter?
지금까지 사귄 남자가 다
천재 아니면 노벨상 수상자야
She only dates geniuses
and Nobel Prize winners.
맙소사, 오늘 찰리와
중국식당에 갔을때
Oh, my God, at the Chinese restaurant
earlier today..
입에 젓가락 끼고
매머드 흉내냈는데!
I put chopsticks in my mouth
and pretended to be a woolly mammoth.
난 그거 재미있던데!
I always loved that.
너야 그렇겠지!
네 뇌는 나보다도 작잖아!
Of course you would!
Your brains are smaller than mine!
찰리의 전 애인들과 난
비교가 안돼
I can't compete with the guys
she goes out with.
수준이 안맞아
They're so out of my league.
맙소사!
Oh, my God!
- 더 나쁜일이 있어?
- 훨씬 나빠!
- Worse?
- Oh, much, much worse.
조운 리버스를 초기 양서류에
빗대서 흉내냈거든!
I did my impression of Joan Rivers
as one of the earliest amphibians.
"우리 걸을까요?"
"Can we walk?"
- 재미있니?
- 아니
- Oh, you like that?
- No.
왜?
What?
봐! 괜찮아!
이거 재미있다니까!
Come on! I think that's funny!
양털매머드잖아
Woolly mammoth.
재밌다니깐!
It's good!
모두들 지금쯤 중간휴식이면
좋겠다고 생각하죠?
I bet you're thinking that now would be
a great time for an intermission, huh?
네, 제발요!
Oh, yes. God, yes.
휴식 같은건 없어요!
Well, you're not gonna get one!
인생에는 휴식 같은게 없다구!
Because in life, there are
no intermissions, people!
제 7장 : 이혼은 엿같은 것!
Now, Chapter 7:
Divorce is a Four-Letter Word!
어떻게 날 떠날수 있지?
How could he leave me?!
몰라요
난 댁이 사랑스러운걸요
I don't know. You seem lovely.
로스? 같이 출연하는 더크야
더크, 내 친구 로스야
Ross, this is one of my costars, Dirk.
Dirk, this is my good friend Ross.
- 반가워요
- 어떤 프로그램에 출연해요?
- Nice to meet you.
- So, what show are you on?
난 배우가 아니라
고생물학과 교수예요
I'm not an actor.
I'm a professor of paleontology.
과학의 일종이야
That's science.
아! 우리 드라마에서
난 과학자로 나와요
Hey, well, listen,
I play a scientist on Days.
얼마전에 드라마 속에서
노벨상을 타기도 했죠
Yeah, my character just won
a Nobel Prize.
로스, 더크가 너와 찰리가
특별한 사이인지 궁금하대
Ross, Dirk was wondering about the woman
you brought and if you guys are together?
오, 그런건 아녜요
Well, no, but..
그런데 그 여자 머리 좋은
남자하고만 데이트해요
I mean, she only goes out
with really, really smart guys.
나 수능점수 690이었어요
Hey, I got a 690 on my SATs.
그정도면 충분하겠네요
I'd lead with that.
브래지어에 사인해주세요
That's it. Just sign right on the bra.
모니카!
Monica!
걱정마!
내년엔 파티에 안나타날게!
Don't worry, Joe.
I won't come next year!
도대체..?
What the..?
그게 뭐야?
What do you got there?
남자들이 전화번호 준거야
Just some boys gave me
their phone numbers.
정말? 어디봐
Oh, really? Let me see.
많기도 하다
Damn, that's a lot of guys.
끼가 다분한걸?
Are you a little slutty?
그런것 같아
I think I am.
이중에 쓸만한 놈이
있는지 내가 봐줄게
Let me see if I approve
of any of these clowns.
이자식은 뻔뻔해
- This guy wears a rug.
- Well..
이친구는 캐나다 출신이야
This guy's Canadian.
이친구는 무슨
종교에 열광하는데
Oh, and this guy is in a cult, okay?
난 5천달러 주고 3급이 됐는데도
차이를 전혀 모르겠어!
It'll cost you $5000 to get to level three,
and I don't feel any different.
통과, 통과, 통과..
Pass. Pa.. Oh, pass. Pass.
- 왜? 이 사람들이 어때서?
- 큰 문제가 있는건 아냐
- Why? What's wrong with these guys?
- Well, nothing major.
하지만 네가 아까워
It's just that, you know,
they're not really good enough for you..
넌 좋은사람 만나야지
and you deserve the best.
고마워, 조이
Joey, you're so sweet.
정말이야, 어쨌든 네가 오늘 누구와
함께 집에 갈지 아니까 상관없어
It's true, but it doesn't matter. I already
know who you're going home with.
누구?
Who?
나
Me.
뭐?
What?
정말?
Really?
우리 같이 살잖아
농담 한거야!
Yeah, because we live together.
It's a joke! It's a joke.
그래! 정말 재밌다!
Right! That's funny! I get it!
너 정말 웃겨, 조이!
- Got you!
- You're funny, Joey.
세상에
Oh, my God.
연극 어땠어?
So how did you enjoy the play?
어머, 챈들러!
정말정말 미안해
Oh, my God.
Honey, I am so, so, so, so sorry.
자기 후회할거야
Well, you should be.
연극 역사상 가장 멋진
세시간을 놓쳤으니까
You missed the most powerful
three hours in the history of the theater.
- 그렇게 좋았어?
- 그럼, 처음엔 물론 별로였어
- You really liked it?
- Oh, yeah. I mean, at first I hated it.
남자는 듣는거에
익숙하지 않잖아!
But why wouldn't l? Because as a man,
I've been trained not to listen!
하지만 제 16장
But after Chapter 16:
"미혼에 뚱보, 사람을
사귀자" 까지 보니까
Fat, Single and Ready to Mingle..
몰입하게 되더라구
I was uplifted.
- 정말?
- 그래
- Oh, really?
- Oh, yeah.
여자들의 일생이 얼마나
놀라운지 미처 몰랐어
I had no idea the amazing journey
you go through as a woman.
자기 초경얘기좀 해줘!
Tell me..
Tell me about your first period.
싫어!
No!
자기 브래지어에 누가
사인했네?
Did somebody sign your bra?
13살때 처음 했어
아주 힘들었지
So I got it when I was 13.
Very difficult.
로스?
그 공룡아가씨 말야
Hey, Ross? So listen,
about you and the dinosaur girl?
정말 노벨상 몇개에 포기할거야?
Are you really just gonna let
a couple of Nobel Prizes scare you off?
기껏 종이쪼가리일 뿐이잖아!
What is that?
Come on, a piece of paper?
상금이 백만 달러야
It's actually a million-dollar prize.
멋지다, 찰리!
Go, Charlie!
하지만 내 요점은..
But my point is..
찰리가 그사람들과 사귄건
사실이지만 헤어지기도 했어
okay, so she dated them,
but she also broke up with them.
어쩌면 평범한 교수정도의
상대를 찾고 있는지도 몰라
Maybe she's looking to, you know,
slum it with some average Joe Ph.D.
그럴지도 모르지, 그리고 난
앞으로 가능성이 많다구
Yeah, maybe, and I do have
my whole career in front of me.
나도..
I mean..
노벨상 탈지 누가 알아?
I could still win a Nobel Prize.
최근에 쓴 논문 2개가
참담한 평을 받기는 했지만
Although the last two papers
I've written were widely discredited.
넌 좋은 두뇌 이상의 장점이 있어
착하고 친절하고 재미있잖아
You're so much more than just brains.
You are sweet and kind and funny.
그리고 섹시하지
And sexy.
찰리에게 그 모든걸
볼수있는 기회를 주라구
Okay, well, give her a chance
to see all that.
네말이 맞아
Yeah. Yeah. You're right.
- 고마워, 찰리를 찾아봐야겠어
- 잘해봐
- Thanks. I'm gonna go find her.
- Good for you.
데본기 평형중단에 관한
네 글은 아주 탁월했어!
And your paper on punctuated equilibrium
in the Devonian Era was topnotch.
내 서류 그만뒤져!
Stop going through my stuff!
너한테 할말있어
나 생각 바꿨어
I just wanted to let you know
I've changed my mind.
해볼래
조이한테 키스할거야
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna kiss Joey.
안돼! 친구들끼리 그러는건
결코 좋은 생각이 아냐!
No! You can't!
Friends hooking up is a bad idea.
뭐 어때?
너랑 챈들러도 했잖아
Please! What about you and Chandler?
그건달라!
난 취했었고 어리석었어!
That's different. I was drunk and stupid.
나도 마찬가지야
Well, hello?
너한테 전화번호 준
남자들도 있잖아!
What about all the guys that you got
the phone numbers from?
- 그중 하나와 키스하지 그래?
- 그럴수도 있지만
- Why don't you just kiss one of them.
- I could..
싫어!
조이랑 키스하고 싶어!
but I don't want to.
I want to kiss Joey.
좋아, 난 큰 실수라고 생각하지만
결정은 네가 하는 거니까
All right. I think it's a big mistake,
but it's your decision.
그래, 할거야
I'm gonna do it.
- 말려도 소용없지?
- 그래
- And I can't stop you?
- No.
그럼, 전화번호라도
넘겨주라
Well, can I at least have
the phone numbers.
혹시 찰리 못봤어?
Hey, Rach, have you seen
Charlie anywhere?
난 조이보다 똑똑해!
I'm smarter than him!
연극표 고마워, 챈들러
Hey, thank you so much
for these tickets, Chandler.
아주 소중한 경험이었어
너희들과 공유하고 싶어
This was a really important experience
for me and I wanted to share it with you.
자긴 정말 멋있어!
You're so wonderful.
왜 날 싫어하지?
Why Don't You Like Me?
제 1장: 나의 초경
Chapter 1: My First Period.
그말을 진짜 믿냐?
고문 좀 당해보시지!
I can't believe you guys bought that.
Enjoy your slow death.